[
  {
    "Front": "ἤ",
    "Back": " konj. $: eller"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἤ - ἤ",
    "Back": " konj. $: enten - eller"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἡγεµών",
    "Back": " sb. 3 m.: leder"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἡγέοµαι",
    "Back": " vb.: fører; mener"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἤδη",
    "Back": " adv.: allerede, nu"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἥδοµαι",
    "Back": " vb. ureg.: glæder mig"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἡδονή",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: glæde"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἡδύς",
    "Back": " adj. 3: sød"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἥκω",
    "Back": " vb.: er kommet, kommer"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἡλικία",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: alder"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἥλιος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: sol"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἧµαι",
    "Back": " vb.: sidder"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἡµεῖς",
    "Back": " pron.: vi"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἠµέρα",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: dag"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἥµισυς",
    "Back": " adj. 3: halv"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἡνίκα",
    "Back": " konj.: når"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἥρως",
    "Back": " sb. 3 m.: helt, heros"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἡσυχία",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: ro, fred"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ἥττων",
    "Back": " adj. 3: mindre"
  }
]